[Music]
how to change data set properties for a
powerbi Telemetry app in
powerbi if you need to change anything
related to the data loading of a powerbi
app on business Central Telemetry you
need to find the workspace for the
report so in the powerbi portal you go
to the workspaces menu and search for
the for the report and there you would
find the underlying workspace which is
where the data set and the report
objects are stored so here I have
business Central Telemetry the Telemetry
app my workspace for that you can see
all the the four uh artifacts
Administration report error report
performance report and usage report and
the data set that is the data foundation
for all of these so in case I need to
change who is refreshing or the refresh
rate or anything this is where it
happens I click the the the more options
here and then I go to
settings and uh in this settings
menu I can now change whoever is
refreshing under data source
credentials edit credentials and now I
can change my credentials here or if I
need to change the the refresh rate of
the report I go to the refresh menu and
change how often the report should
refresh as well as notifications of
refresh errors you can set that here as
[Music]
well